ISABELLA POTAPENKO

isabellapotapenko@gmail.com

509-847-4479

My goal in my professional development is to continue empathizing with people-- understanding their wants, needs, motivations, struggles, and what brings them joy. Through my experience in customer service and hospitality, I have learned how important it is to always listen and to never stop asking questions.

SKILLS

Figma

00000

Sketch

00000

Adobe

00000

MIRO

00000

Wireframing

00000

Prototyping

00000

User Research

00000

User Testing

00000

Google Workspace

00000

Problem Solving

00000

Interpersonal Skills

00000

Leadership

00000

Attention to Detail

00000

Public Speaking

00000

Russian Proficency

00000

EXPERIENCE

Wyckoff House Museum (New York)

Administrative Coordinator/ Bookkeeper-- July 2022- Present

- Write and apply for grants
- · Maintain existing grants
- Maintain deadlines and organize staff to meet those deadlines
- Monitor and record income and expenses in Quickbooks
- Reconcile bank accounts monthly, manage cash flow quarterly
- · Process payroll, write checks, handle petty cash

Appfolio (Remote)

Leasing AI Operator-- Sept 2021-Present

- Engage with leasing prospects via text to ensure concerns are resolved
- Assist leasing AI in converting prospective leads into scheduled appointments
- Provide quality feedback to management for product development

New Museum Store (New York)

Key holder/ Buyer/ Social Media Manager -- Dec 2021- July 2022

- Managed store operations
- · Curated product selection
- · Received and process inventory
- Managed social media content, including photography and photo editing
- Worked with local and international vendors/artists

Black Fox Coffee (New York)

General Manager -- July 2018 - Sept 2021

- Was responsible for labor cost/COGS management
- Was responsible for managing staff and high volume environment
- Conducted interviews and onboard new staff members
- Demonstrated ability to efficiently problem solve
- Demonstrated strong interpersonal skills with customers and staff members
- Responsible for ordering inventory/ stock-take
- Responsible for creating and updating all training materials

MAÑANA (Austin)

General Manager -- March 2016 - June 2018

- Managed company budget
- Managed invoices via Plate IQ software
- Created weekly staff schedule
- Managed staff and shop maintenance
- Ordered products and managed inventory
- Demonstrated specialty coffee skills

South Congress Hotel - Lobby Shop (Austin)

Buyer/ Manager -- March 2017 - Dec 2017

- Curated the shop's product collection
- Managed staff and shop display
- · Demonstrated retail and sales skills
- · Worked with local and commercial artists

EDUCATION

CAREERFOUNDRY- UX DESIGN PROGRAM--CERTIFICATION, SEPT 2023

NEW SCHOOL- VISUAL STUDIES-- BA, summa cum laude, 2020

Minor in Curatorial Studies